[{"answer": "my friend wasn't his only son. my friend was his son, too", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, they only kill them when they love them...", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I'd say nothing. After two or three, people will try to find a pattern. A reason", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Isn't that what we want? that place all over again? Only done right this time..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I work at the Big Boy warehouse. In that place. I drive a for", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I just read it...", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend. And you are...", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Are they still together", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Is he a Nazi", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Is he a Nazi", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What's he care about", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Who's this", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "After your mother died, that's when you stopped going to shul. Doing your homework. Everything", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "'Cause they got rid of my friend. He knew how to deal with the assholes. that place, please..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " What's that go to do with...I've gone out with a, with Jewish women. Why", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Notice? Like what...", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Did you know that there was a that place reporter there that night", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I didn't notice his shoes.... Did your mother know he was there", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Ham and cheese on white", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What the hell do you have", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "We have a problem here", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Religion isn't about making sense. It's about", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Shut up.  What did you do", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What could he have done?? You fucking kikes..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I want you to say kaddish for her. It's the only thing she asked from us...", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You do it on the inside...", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I don't do that", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Don't tell me what I", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You do it on the inside...", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "...I want you to do it on the outside, too", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No, you don't.... If you hated them, you'd study them, so you'd know why you hate them. You know what tefillin is? my friend? Shotness? You know the kaddish from the kiddush?  my friend? He went to that place. He studied the Torah, the Talmud, the that place, the whole bit. He hated Jews", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Who's my friend?!!", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I have a job", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You gave fifty thousand to that college magazine", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " ...Look, he's a skinhead", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " Believe me, my friend's the racist kind. Are you a fascist, my friend? Yes or no", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "They're racist, they're militaristic, they act like bullyboys in the territories...", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "They had my friend and my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You don't know that. There's no", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "They sound like you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "I work in the DA's office. You go to those meetings, half the people there are informants", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Which Times guy", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Christianity's silly, but at least there's something to believe in. Or not believe. Judaism there's nothing", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What's it about", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Who knows what that is", "docId": "Believer_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Can anybody imagine why I would say a Jewish prayer", "qsentId": 48}]